

♥ Thu Duc, Ho Chi Minh City☒ datnb4@gmail.com

(+84) 3527 29542 github.com/datnguyenute

## SUMMARY

4 years experience as web developer, including 2+ years working as a front-end developer skillful with Javascript, Angular 2+ and Typescript.

Meticulous about developing interface features, love to work with high-professional and dynamic team to enhance my skills together with contributing toward team's performance.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# **Software Engineer**

FPT Software | May 2020 - Jun 2022

#### MNES

Develop and maintain management system and Xray analysis system for Japanese hospitals.

Project technicals: Angular, Golang and Google Cloud with Scrum in the development process.

Role: Full-stack Developer.

Pickup requirements, communicate with customers and onsite, analyze and finalize the best solutions

Implement new features, fix the remained defects of legacy system by customizing the Cornerstone library.

Collaborate with offshore members and onsite in daily work.

Carry on instruction new team members and guide interns.

Review the code of team members as frequent practice to improve code quality and check the correction of dependencies in the system.

# FPT Software | Feb 2020 - May 2020

#### FutureNet

Develop and maintain a management system for a Japanese hospital.

Project technicals: VueJs, dotNet.

Role: Front-end Developer.

Implement UI features as customer request and assist other development team members promptly in fixing UI defects by using VueJS.

Optimize UI code for legacy system and cross-review with teammates to ensure codes quality. Invoke in a Scrum team and handle sudden issues in the most appropriate action.

## FPT Software | Nov 2019 - Feb 2020

#### LOOKREC V2

Develop a new management system for medicine and study of a Japanese hospital chain.

Project technicals: Angular, NodeJS, Golang, Google Cloud with Scrum in the development process.

Role: Front-end Developer.

Design UI and implement features by using Angular 6.

Pick up user stories, analyze, design, discuss with team members to tackle them, and write documentation to clarify my work.

Peer to peer review source code, discuss together and find the best solution to enhance the code performance.

# FPT Software | Oct 2018 - May 2019

#### DSM

Develop a website to connect dental clinics and tele-radiology centers for remote radio diagnosis services.

Project technicals: ¡Query KendoUI, PHP.

Role: Front-end Developer.

Pickup requirements, analyze, discuss with team members to finalize the expected result and the best way to implement.

Mostly implement UI features with jQuery KendoUI.

Collaborate with backend teams to integrate front-end and RESTful API.

Invoke in Scrum team.

# FPT Software | Jun 2018 - Oct 2018

#### Davis

Develop web management system in AI application technology field for Korean healthcare organization.

Project technicals: jQuery KendoUI, PHP.

Role: Full-stack Developer.

Develop and build common UI components by using KendoUI for other members to use effectively and implement correctly.

Collaborate with team, discuss and build complete features using KendoUI and Codeigniter.

Invoke in Scrum team, attend sudden meetings to handle unexpected problems and come up with the most suitable way-out.

### ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

#### **HCMUTE**

Bachelor of Software Engineering | Aug 2014 - Aug 2018

### **JobFind - Project**

A website where employers can contact employees who have demand on seeking for a job and give them an environment for submitting and respond job application.

Project technicals: PHP Laravel, MongoDB

Role: Full-stack Developer.

Responsible for building features for employers visualization.

Collaborate with teammates to analyze database design, draw flowcharts and use case diagrams.

Cross review among team members to improve code quality and enhance code performance.

Analyze and figure out solutions to accumulate user's experience with modern UI.

# SKILLS

Soft skills: Time management, critical-thinking, collaboration.

English skills: Good enough to communicate and write.

JS Framework: Angular2+.

Programming languages: Javascript, Typescript, HTML, CSS, SCSS. Database: MongoDB, PostgreSQL, MySQL, Datastore(Google Cloud).

Addition skills: Git, Scrum. IDEs: Visual Studio Code.

Others: PrimeNG, RxJs, KendoUI.